let questions = [
      {
        numb: 1,
        question: "36, 34, 30, 28,___, 22 What number should come to fill in the blank space?",
        answer: "24",
        options: [
          "24",
          "26",
          "25",
          "None of the above"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the largest prime palindrome(Roman Numbers)?",
        answer: "19",
        options: [
          "1",
          "5",
          "71",
          "19"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 3,
        question: "n! has n digits.What is n?(n is an integer)",
        answer: "22",
        options: [
          "22",
          "21",
          "23",
          "24"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which is the only number that is spelt with letters arranged in alphabetical order?",
        answer: "40",
        options: [
          "30",
          "20",
          "1",
          "40"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 5,
        question: "str(n*n)+str(n*n*n) has all the digits(0 to 9).What is n?",
        answer: "69",
        options: [
          "69",
          "73",
          "23",
          "29"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which is the only number that is spelt with letters arranged in alphabetical(reverse) order?",
        answer: "1",
        options: [
          "30",
          "20",
          "1",
          "40"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which is the first number that has 'a' in it's spelling?",
        answer: "1000",
        options: [
          "10000",
          "100",
          "1000",
          "10000"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 8,
        question: "The integer n has n letters in it's spelling?",
        answer: "4",
        options: [
          "5",
          "7",
          "4",
          "11"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Every ______ number has 'e' in it's spelling?",
        answer: "odd",
        options: [
          "even",
          "prime",
          "composite",
          "odd"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "The only number that is not represented by the Roman numerals?",
        answer: "0",
        options: [
          "0",
          "1000000",
          "100000000",
          "10000000000"
        ]
      },
    ];